elfwood.com 2015-03-18

# Elfwood Fantasy and Sci fi art

Your privacy is important to us. Please take a moment to read through our Privacy Policy that will tell you a bit about how we handle the information you supply and what other information we collect.

General for all information submitted to Elfwood is that we will never release name or other personal information about a Member without the permission of that Member. We reserve the right to distribute aggregated demographic information provided by Members.

## Information we collect

In the registration process you submit personal data. This is called “Personally Identifiable Information,” and could be for example your name, age, and e-mail address. From time to time in the future we may offer additional features, services, and promotional opportunities that would require you to submit Personally Identifiable Information to participate.

We also collect what is called “Anonymous Information”, exemplified by your IP address, the type of browser you use, the pages on our Sites that you have visited, and the advertisements that you have clicked on. WE DO NOT match your Personally Identifiable Information to your Anonymous Information. What you do and where you go is your business only. We use this aggregated information solely to be able to optimize the website based on how our visitors use it.

## Cookies

Like many Internet sites, we also use “cookies”. We do this to better support services for registered users and to collect statistics on how our website is used. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer and is stored on your hard drive. When you visit our Site(s) the cookie identifies your computer to us so that you do not have to re-register each time you visit. We may also use cookies to measure the traffic to our Sites and the use of different services and features of the Sites. Advertisers that appear on Elfwood may place cookies on your computer and their use of the information stored on those cookies is subject to their own privacy policies. You should visit their sites to learn about their information practices. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Elfwood cookies.

You can enable cookies in your browser. This might result in loss of some features on elfwood.com, for example login for registered users. Please also note that other websites that uses cookies might not be able to perform its best with cookies turned off.

## Password Security

We strive for having really secure transfers between your computer and Elfwood. Any actions requiring your password is sent using https. Despite our efforts, Elfwood encourages Members to change their passwords frequently.

## Communication

Postings and other communications with Elfwood are not private and may be published and edited at the discretion of Elfwood unless specifically instructed otherwise.
